https://ukskydiving.com/privacy-policy/

SEE BELOW FOR OUR
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how North London Skydiving Centre Limited uses and protects any information that you give us.
North London Skydiving Centre Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
North London Skydiving Centre Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This current policy is effective from 25th May 2018.
What we collect – We may collect the following information: name, contact information including email address, demographic information such as your address and postcode.
What we do with the information we gather – We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping – We may periodically need to email or text you information directly relating to the services and products you have requested from us such as weather information and special instructions. We may also from time to time send you promotional emails and texts about similar services and events we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Security – We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies – A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. The cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites- Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting only if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to North London Skydiving Centre Limited, Chatteris Airfield, Block Fen Drove, Wimblington, March, Cambridgshire PE15 0FB.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us [office@ukskydiving.com] as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
ALSO CHECK OUT
THE  EXPERIENCE
PRICES
VOUCHERS
LAST MINUTE OFFERS
£20 OFF CHARITY JUMPS
AIR TO AIR FILMING
FAQ'S
OK lET'S DO THIS!
BOOK YOUR SKYDIVE
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. Please select your preference. Cookie settingsRejectACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
